[♪ opening theme song playing]
[grunts]
That was a daemon.
Yes, I think so. Good eye.
Pull over.
I'd like a closer look.
Right.
It's a beautiful evening, ma'am.
And that's a fine companion
you've got there.
[Yozakura growls]
[WOMAN] Uh?
You can see them?
Feathers as black
as the night sky
and a fearsome horned skull.
A handsome daemon,
if I may be so bold.
What's their name?
[woman gasps]
[Yozakura growls]
[woman crying]
Finally...
You're the first person I've met
who doesn't think I'm crazy.
♪
[GONZO]
Of course I don't.
I'm just like you.
[chuckles softly]
[WOMAN] Uh?
[gasps]
[YOZAKURA] Hm. Hm.
[woman sighs]
♪
[YOZAKURA] We are Kin'u-gyokuto.
[WOMAN] This one is named
Yozakura.
[GONZO] Hmm.
I don't see their other half.
[WOMAN] Asagiri.
They don't like the night,
so they're hiding.
[sighs] I see.
And what are you doing out here
on the bridge at this hour?
It's dangerous.
[WOMAN] I was thinking
about jumping.
Ending it all.
It's not as though
anybody needs me around.
[YOZAKURA] If you were to fall,
I would catch you in an instant.
You must live.
[WOMAN] Forgive me.
I'm so sorry. [cries]
I shouldn't be saying
such things to you. We just met.
[GONZO]
Please, you're fine.
It must be fate that I happened
to pass by here.
I'm happy to sit and talk
if you'd like
to share some more.
♪
I'm Gonzo Kagemori, by the way.
[WOMAN] Oh, I'm Iori Shingo.
You're really convinced
nobody needs you?
Uh, it's true.
I've never been able
to do anything right,
even as a child.
I failed my parents every way
I possibly could.
Like, not getting
into a good school.
No surprise, since I'm stupid.
Even my older brother says so.
They all treat me like I never
should have been born
in the first place.
So, yeah.
I think the world would be
a better place if I was gone.
♪
I've thought about this a lot.
In fact, I tried to die once
and couldn't even do that right.
♪
I met my companions
when I went into the mountains
looking for a place
to end my life.
There,
I stumbled across their relic.
It didn't have hands or a head,
but something about it
was breathtaking.
I don't know much
about gods or Buddhas,
but I guess I kind of thought...
if I were to die in front
of such a statue,
maybe it would escort my soul
to heaven.
♪
So I slit my wrist, but then...
Your two daemons appeared.
That's right.
They're very kind
and excellent listeners.
I told them
about my struggles in life.
Later,
my family overheard me
talking to them,
which didn't go well.
They were sure I'd lost my mind.
♪
I tried to explain
what daemons are,
but that was hopeless
since they couldn't see them.
They thought
I was hallucinating,
hearing things, sick.
So I revealed them to my family,
thinking that would help.
Instead, they called them
devils and evil spirits.
They said I'd been possessed
by monsters.
And before long,
I was even more ostracized.
Only my brother
seemed interested,
though I'm still not sure why.
[YOZAKURA] He cannot be trusted!
He pretends to understand
only because he wishes
to work us to death
for his own benefit.
He would take
advantage of you, Iori.
You must cut ties
with the Shingos!
What life is there
without my family?
This world has no use
for people like me.
[exhales]
♪
This is sudden, but I would like
to invite you into my home.
Uh, huh?
The Kagemoris are a pretty
big clan, growing every day.
We're always on the lookout
for new members
and people to join us.
All right. That said,
I'm a total stranger to you.
We have plenty
of other employees
who come from backgrounds
and situations similar to yours.
Many of them are Wielders
like yourself.
You'll find we're
an incredibly welcoming group.
[chuckles]
That's especially true
when someone has daemons.
[ASA] Brother, your shoulder...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think I'll be fine.
I can still move my arm.
Wait, were you shot
with a rifle?
You need proper treatment.
But if we go
to a regular doctor,
they'd ask probing questions
and get the police involved,
which would cause
all kinds of problems.
[Yuru gasps]
Plus, you don't have
any insurance,
so treatment would be
super expensive.
Wait, I don't want that.
Hana would never forgive me.
[ASA] There's only
one thing left.
You're coming back to the manor!
[YURU] Why would I?
Because Dr. Sakurazawa
can treat you in the infirmary.
Plus, she's used to dealing
with stuff like this.
Huh? The woman
who steals your blood?
Hold on, are you even positive
that she's a real doctor?
'Cause I am not.
And besides...
It's not like I can trust
the Kagemoris
-in the first place.
-[grunting]
[YURU] Thanks, but I'm gonna
have to pass.
[ASA] You're being
so mean, brother.
You have so much faith in them.
You sure that's wise?
Yes, of course I am.
I get it.
They're a little strange.
And they aren't like others
down here.
But that's for the best.
Normal people don't last long
in this world.
Like I told you before,
it was the master
and Jin who saved me
from Higashi Village assassins.
[YURU] Jin? Hm...
He didn't deny
that he was responsible
for the attack on the village.
Even when I was holding
a machete to his neck.
[ASA] Exactly. He's earnest
in the strangest ways.
When it comes
to the three brothers,
he's the one who plays the role
of the bad guy
to protect the Kagemoris.
Every time. Without fail.
He stays detached
and avoids empathizing
with foes and subordinates.
It's like he suppresses
his emotions
for the sake of the clan.
He does what he must.
And what about the other two?
[ASA] Hagure teaches me
new skills
so that one day I'll be able
to live a normal life.
It's been really helpful.
He showed me how to draw manga.
Those are, uh, picture books.
You could say they're like
modern woodblock prints.
He lets me help him
with his work.
That way, I can earn money
inside the barrier
where it's safe.
[YURU] Wow, that's nice.
And Asuma...
His smile looks fake.
He's the least trustworthy
one of the whole bunch.
[ASA] Did he stand there with
that serene look on his face
and ask if you wanted to die?
[YURU] Oh. Oh, yeah, he did!
Asuma thinks if people are going
to keep trying to kill you,
you should just let it happen.
That way, you can acquire
more power
so you're able
to protect yourself better.
He also argues that people
like us should be subject
to the oversight
of a powerful organization,
one like the Kagemoris,
for example.
He may say unsettling things,
but he doesn't lie to us.
I really do believe that.
[ASUMA] What shall we do
with the girl?
Return her to Higashi?
[Dera sighs]
I'm afraid she's seen and heard
too much down here.
If we took her back
to the village,
we'd have to make sure
she doesn't say--
[GONZO]
You'd throw her in a cell?
♪
Is there a way
she can keep her freedom?
The children of Higashi village
don't know the twins'
secret yet.
They have no idea
that Asa and Yuru
gain immense power
by dying.
People are only
let in on the truth
once they've gotten older.
It's how the villagers
recognize you as an adult.
I seriously doubt Azami
understands anything.
[FUYUKI]
So they do share the secret.
[GONZO] Learning it means
you've entered adulthood
and are an official member
of the village.
They're creating unity
by making people think
they've been given
special knowledge.
[Gonzo grunts]
That could be hard to accept.
And what if somebody questions
the village's ways?
Anyone who dissents
is kicked down the mountain
under the guise that they're
being sent here to work.
They survive by doing
whatever odd jobs
associates of the village
are able to scrounge up.
Huh? Hold on a minute.
A lot of people left the village
for work.
Are you saying
they never came back 'cause--
[DERA] If they were
allowed to return,
they might reveal the truth
to Yuru.
Don't get me wrong,
there are some guys
who come down here looking
for legitimate employment.
[sighs]
The Kagemoris usually
kill them, though.
Make no mistake.
We both have plenty of blood
on our hands.
The Taderas have murdered
many of our people as well.
[Dera chuckles]
[Gonzo chuckles]
[both laugh]
[RIGHT] Uh?
Hey, you two have
a nice chat in there?
-Sure did.
-You did a great job. Thank you.
[Daifuku
and Ohagi squeal]
[ASA] Oh, Master! My brother
has a pretty bad wound.
I'd like him to be treated
back home.
I never agreed to go with you!
Sorry, but we can't.
I'll have to deal
with Akio first thing.
I'd prefer if Yuru
didn't have to see that.
Oh. I had almost forgotten.
[YURU] Akio? The bald guy
who wanted me dead?
[GONZO]
We tracked down the traitor
at the manor earlier.
It was Akio after all.
Ah. So Jin's suspicion
was correct.
Though, it's strange.
I'd think my uncle
would've told me
if he were in league with Akio,
yet his name never came up.
That night Yuru visited us,
it was my uncle
who tipped me off
that both twins
would be in the same place.
He said Ivan was the one
who told him,
and that they were sending
some mercs he scraped together.
He suggested that's when
I should betray you.
Well, I of course
ignored his message
and pretended to be asleep.
You left him on unread?
If not Shingo, then Akio
must know Ivan personally.
-[gasps] Ivan!
-I got it.
Akio's working with the guy
who knows about our parents.
Which means he might know
something, too.
[FUYUKI] Master...
We should return at once.
If they have any info,
I will get it out of them.
[clattering]
[Hagure gasps]
[screams]
My studio!
My work!
That computer had my drafts!
[GABBY] Yeah, a fight broke out.
That's a big whoops from us.
But not everything's gone.
The coffee maker's still okay.
You want me to make you a cup?
A curse upon you
and all your family,
that every last cup of coffee
you drink
turns into ink
for the rest of your life!
Where are the files? [groans]
They're safe. Good.
[GABBY] Even if they were gone,
couldn't you have
just redrawn them
with Black and White?
Mm... You don't get it.
Imperfections of a manga drawn
by hand are what make it good.
I'm not so sure about that.
I like it sharp.
When everything
clicks into place.
But that doesn't feel
true to life.
When I create my characters,
it's what I try
to pay attention to the most.
[running footsteps]
It's more real when their hearts
wobble and waver.
Jin! Please, listen to me!
There's gotta be something
you can do to save Akio!
There isn't a chance.
The old man would never forgive
someone who betrayed us.
Akio will die for what he did.
We've been together
ever since we were kids.
We may not be related by blood,
but he's my brother!
I know there's no way
the master would listen to me.
But if it came from his son,
then he would--
[JIN] Haruo.
We can't keep
threats around the manor.
It puts yours and everyone
else's lives at risk.
Akio can't be allowed to live.
[Haruo gasps]
[clattering]
[SAKURAZAWA] There's not much
I can do about a severed arm.
I stopped the bleeding.
You want more than that,
take him to the hospital.
To think my own kid brother
was the one
who betrayed our clan. [sighs]
This sucks.
[AKIO] You think it's just me?
I could have a whole network
in the manor.
Everyone else here already
let Fuyuki's Blacklist
comb through
their personal info.
When the suspicion around you
grew too large to ignore,
we were all subject to doubt,
so we went through
every last person in our employ.
You're the only one
we haven't checked.
You did this alone.
[AKIO] Does that mean
they checked you too, Doc?
[SAKURAZAWA] Sure did.
I've got nothing to hide.
So why did you do it, Akio?
You know full well the master
gives no quarter
to those who would turn
their back on the clan.
Once he gets home
and he has the info he needs,
you will be executed.
We can't bail you
out of this one.
Did you just hate working
for the Kagemoris?
Can't say I love this life
of crime we live myself.
I'd quit in a heartbeat
if I had a way out.
But still!
If I did, you'd never see me
sell out my friends!
[sighs]
So why'd you do it, Akio?
[Akio sighs]
[AKIO] Look, you know
what's wrong with me.
My body's been messed up
since birth,
so I can't feel any pain.
As a kid,
it made me unstoppable.
I didn't know
my physical limits,
so no one could ever beat me
in a fight.
Just as I couldn't feel
my own pain,
I didn't understand
the pain of others.
I'm grateful to the Kagemoris
for raising and hiring
a delinquent like me.
If I'd gone
into the world like this,
I'm sure I would've gotten
the death sentence
a long time ago.
But living here was easy,
because everyone else
is crazy, too.
With all these weird daemons,
there's never been
a dull moment.
[Midori grunts]
I even had my siblings.
You guys were
like a family to me.
And that was fun, I guess.
But it still felt
like something was missing.
That "something"
never disappeared.
And each day,
with every step I took, it grew.
Eventually, I searched online
for people like me.
And wouldn't you know,
there really was a community
for us freaks
who couldn't feel pain.
On the forums,
I found someone who might be
one of my parents.
♪
I felt an emotion
I had never felt before.
Don't tell me, you reached out?
So it was them.
They put these ideas
in your head.
Akio! Your parents
abandoned you as a kid.
What do you get
out of seeing them now?
Why would you bother?
They might just be
trying to use you
for their own benefit!
[AKIO] Natsuki, I need a favor.
Let Mountain God go. Right now.
What? You know
that's not happening.
Fuyuki has to get their info.
[AKIO] I beg you.
Mountain God will be destroyed.
They'll die.
[NATSUKI]
Destroyed? Who would do that?
No one here has any reason
to hurt your relics.
Not after
you've already dissolved
your contract with them.
So what are you talking about?
[running footsteps]
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
-[panting]
-One, two.
-[BUNBUN] Found them!
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four...
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two. One, two.
Good, Mountain God
survived the fall.
Even if by a hare's breadth!
[both whooping]
I'm sorry about this, friends,
but we've gotta take a hop
to Fuyuki for interrogation.
Gotta roll up my little sleeves!
[grunting]
-[TSUGAI 1] Heave-Ho!
-[TSUGAI 2] Heave-Ho!
[TSUGAI 1] Huh?
♪
It's gonna...
-[both gasp]
-[Bunbun grunting]
-[explosion]
-[both gasp]
-[JIN] Mm...
-[gasps]
[rumbling]
[tsugais grunting]
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four...
-[both] Mm...
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four...
[Bunbun coughs]
Hey, Heave-Ho?
That kinda hurts, you know.
[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
But you two are fine,
aren't you?
-[TSUGAI 2] Three, four...
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
Oh, good. It was worth it.
[grunting]
-Ouchies.
-[TSUGAI 1] One, two...
[BUNBUN] It's busted.
I can't walk.
[breathes shakily]
Yamakaze is shattered.
Hm?
Where's Tanikaze?
They're not here!
[squelching]
[squelching continues]
♪
[JIN] We're on our way
to the scene.
Something blew up
near the main gate.
Has anything changed there?
Nothing to report right now.
We're gonna stay on high alert
in the infirmary.
[BABAMARU] A daemon attack?
Too early to say.
[BABAMARU] That's the problem
with a manor like this.
With so many daemons,
we can't tell
when an outsider arrives.
-[door slides open]
-[NATSUKI] Mm?
♪
Hold on. What's this?
That's Tanikaze.
How did they get here?
[running footsteps]
[tsugais yelling]
Everybody!
-Get down!
-[Midori grunts]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[NATSUKI] He protected you
like he should.
[KEN] "We're all the same.
None of us can live alone."
[ASA] Being betrayed by someone
this close really stings.